

# LA TORRE ROMERO JOSE LUIS

# **Freelancer**

Software Engineering Student

# About me

Young student with knowledge in frontend, backend, and IoT development. I have work experience as a junior full-stack developer. Additionally, I have participated in teams working with full-stack technologies, mobile development, IoT, and AI.



+51 941 831 923



joselatorre143351@gmail.com



https://github.com/AdminLTR



https://adminltr.github.io/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jose-luis-latorre-romero-7bb5442a6/

#### **SKILLS**

#### **FRONTEND**











**BACKEND** 

#### **INTERNET OF THINGS**









#### **EXTRA**







React Native

**MOBILE** 

## **EDUCATION**

#### National Universtity of San Marcos - Peru

2022 - Actualmente Currently in 3rd year of Software Engineering at UNMSM Peru

# **LANGUAGES**

Spanish (Native)



• English(B2)



• Italian (B2)



• Portuguese (B2)



German (A1)



## **EXPERIENCE**

# NEXUS APP Automation Script

Enero 2024

Freelance developer specializing in scripting, automation, report generation, and desktop applications.

Technologies: Python, Pandas, Excel, Tkinter

# CapitalFork

Currency Exchange System Julio 2024 - Agosto 2024

https://capitalfork.com/

Junior Full-stack Developer specializing in bug fixing, maintenance, and feature implementation.

Technologies: JQuery, Laravel, AJAX, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap

#### **Eneisoft**

National Meeting of Software Engineering Students Octubre 2024 - Noviembre 2024

https://eneisoft.org/

Development team, freelance full-stack developer. Expertise in designing and developing landing pages, data structuring, deployment, SEO, and process automation.

Technologies: JQuery, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap

# VITA Academy

VITA - Preuniversity academy Noviembre 2024

https://academiapreuniversitariavita.com/

Freelance Frontend Developer. Specializing in design, development, deployment, and SEO.

Technologies: JQuery, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **SmartTachito**

SmartTachito is an intelligent trash bin, powered by Artificial Intelligence and the Internet of Things.

The bin features an artificial intelligence model capable of classifying waste through image recognition. It can sort the trash into different compartments based on the model's response.

The project is undergoing continuous research and has received recognition from both UNMSM and UNI to date

**Topics**: Arduino, ESP32, Django, OpenCV, Tensorflow

# **BillyApp**

Smart security system based on Artificial Intelligence and the Internet of Things.

It consists of a surveillance camera system equipped with an integrated artificial intelligence model capable of detecting all types of weapons, including knives, blades, firearms, and more.

**Topics**: Arduino, ESP32, Django, OpenCV, Tensorflow, React, Mapbox